<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Hi! This is kiriloler</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Hi! This is kiriloler</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Hugo Theme Stack Starter</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:22:30 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>TPH</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/tph/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:22:30 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/tph/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/tph/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post TPH" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;introduction&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>T.P.H.</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/t.p.h./</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:16:45 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/t.p.h./</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/t.p.h./cover.png" alt="Featured image of post T.P.H." /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T.P.H.&lt;/strong&gt; is a 2D horror game incorporated with art styles of weirdcore and analog horror. Players will navigate the scientific department of T.P.H., a &lt;font color=Red&gt;deadly&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color=Red&gt;dreamy&lt;/font&gt; place. The core mechanics of &lt;strong&gt;T.P.H.&lt;/strong&gt; is interacting with different text descriptions to obtain tools and discover puzzles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More Infos
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link to itch.io: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://kiriloler.itch.io/tph&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://kiriloler.itch.io/tph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;text-based-games&#34;&gt;Text-Based Games
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In most games, texts are messengers of stories. In those text-based games, however, they are interactable objects. After playing several fantastic text-based games, I said to myself: &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t this mechanic a perfect match for puzzle games?&amp;rdquo; And that is the inspiration of &lt;strong&gt;T.P.H.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align = center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;2.jpg&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;3.png&#34; width=50% height=50%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;weirdcore&#34;&gt;Weirdcore
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weirdcore to me is a complex sensation. It creates a sense of belonging in an alienated place. When I look at weirdcore images, I can often found elements that are nostalgic or childish: toys, seesaws, slides, birthday cakes&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;all those childhood items are familiar to me, but only one thing is strange：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody is here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s right. What makes weirdcore weird is not the its presented items, but its absence in life. Those art pieces are the representations of the childhood playgrounds I had forfeited and abandoned, left with only vague memories that confuses me. I had grown up, with new interests and ambitions, but I shall never forget the happy moments I had with my old friends—they takes a precious part of my soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I know &lt;strong&gt;T.P.H.&lt;/strong&gt; is a horror game. But besides from thrills and creepiness, I also hope to help some players to retrieve their childhood memories, memories that can support them at dark times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align = center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;1.png&#34; width=60%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;4.png&#34; width=60%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;5.png&#34; width=60%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;analog-horror&#34;&gt;Analog Horror
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was introduced to the concept Analog Horror from the game &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tejas-joshi.itch.io/examination-of-fear&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Examination of Fear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A truly uncanny game where the players simply needs to evaluate whether a picture is scary. I was so obsessed with such art style and immediately determined to incorporate it into &lt;strong&gt;T.P.H.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-perfect-human&#34;&gt;The Perfect Human
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plot of this game is rather vague, but I actually invested a lot of efforts on it. The story is centered around the concept of &amp;ldquo;TPH&amp;rdquo;, an abbreviation for &amp;ldquo;The Perfect Human&amp;rdquo;. What I want to share from this story is some insights on &lt;em&gt;perfection&lt;/em&gt;. What is &lt;em&gt;perfection&lt;/em&gt;? Does &lt;em&gt;perfection&lt;/em&gt; actually exists? If so, is it truly perfect?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rainthm</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/rainthm/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 19:40:42 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/rainthm/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/rainthm/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Rainthm" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rainthm&lt;/strong&gt;(Rain + Rhythm) is a platformer + rhythm game set in a futuristic pixel world. Players can control &lt;em&gt;Ash&lt;/em&gt;, the cyber witch, to move around the map and slash falling notes(Rains) on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More infos:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link to itch.io: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://kiriloler.itch.io/rainthm&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://kiriloler.itch.io/rainthm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trailer: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://youtu.be/7wGTYPIoTkg&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://youtu.be/7wGTYPIoTkg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Playthrough: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://youtu.be/oCYSl_lJfpQ&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://youtu.be/oCYSl_lJfpQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;narrating&#34;&gt;Narrating
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have tried out the game, you probably can tell that the narrative style is inspired from &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://katanazero.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Katana Zero&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (If u haven&amp;rsquo;t played it I strongly recommend) One of my favorite aspect of &lt;strong&gt;Katana Zero&lt;/strong&gt; is its intriguing story: &lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoiler Alert&lt;/strong&gt;: Will reveal plots of both &lt;strong&gt;Katana Zero&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Rainthm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the protagonist, code name &lt;em&gt;Dragon&lt;/em&gt;, falls asleep at night, the narrative often flashes back to a distant past where, a little boy and girl were haunted by a mysterious figure. The scene will end abruptly, then repeats again and again when &lt;em&gt;Dragon&lt;/em&gt; goes to bed, each time with some slight changes or progressions. On the first thought, I simply assumes that the little boy must be &lt;em&gt;Dragon&lt;/em&gt;, but in the last repetition of the scene it was revealed that the mysterious figure is the &lt;em&gt;Dragon&lt;/em&gt; instead. Such twist of the plot had a stunning effect in which I can never forget. So, in &lt;strong&gt;Rainthm&lt;/strong&gt;, I used similar techniques to trike the players into thinking the flashbacks are relating to the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s past, but actually something else.&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;narrative.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ash&#34;&gt;Ash
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ash&lt;/em&gt; is the protagonist, the cool cyber witch. Her name is transformed from the Overwatch character &lt;em&gt;Ashe&lt;/em&gt;. They also share likewise appearances: both got white hairs and a hat. &lt;em&gt;Ash&lt;/em&gt; is a cold warrior with heart. She don&amp;rsquo;t speak much, but she do cares about the corruptions in the society and is willing to fight for it. If I have to use some words to describe her, I would say: A lonely rebel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ash.png&#34; width=30% height=30%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;ash2.png&#34; width=30% height=30%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;animation&#34;&gt;Animation
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is my first time to use pixel art in my game. As it turns out, pixel art is much harder than I thought. With a few pixels, a fabulous pixel artist can form a decent structure of an item, which takes a lot of practice. For me, I almost gone mad trying to capture the flow of hairs and movement of feet. Thanks to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.aseprite.org/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aseprite&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a software specialized for pixel arts, I can do my job much easier and quicker. Even so, it still takes me almost a half day to finish the running animation of Ash(which is only 9 images lol) Anyways, this is definitely a sweet experience that improves my art skills, and I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of myself making those animations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;WAR.gif&#34; width=30%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;Witchgirl_Attack_Left.gif&#34; width=30%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;exp.gif&#34; width=30%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Let Me Do It For You</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/let-me-do-it-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 18:40:39 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/let-me-do-it-for-you/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/let-me-do-it-for-you/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Let Me Do It For You" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let Me Do It For You&lt;/strong&gt; is a weird platformer about a dog who can extend his nose and, not only the nose can stretch GREAT GREAT GREAT distance, it can also change directions lmao.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More Infos:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link to itch.io: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://zeenaz.itch.io/let-me-do-it-for-you&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://zeenaz.itch.io/let-me-do-it-for-you&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;memes&#34;&gt;Memes
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the title one can tell that this game is inspired from the Borzoi Dog meme. Personally I have nothing much to say about this theme, it is cute and really, really funny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;player_walk_2.png&#34; width=30%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;growth&#34;&gt;Growth
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the former experiences in mind, I am able to finished my tasks quicker and smoother this time. I also managed to study new components of Unity when facing unfamiliar problems. When creating the nose stretching effects, I researched and find a Unity component called Line Renderer that can draw textured lines. Using scripts to control this component, the body of the nose is drawn as the nose head moves, creating the effect of nose stretching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;3.png&#34; width=100%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;important-lessons&#34;&gt;Important Lessons
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always make backup files before making CRAZY changes to the codes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some mechanics are just complex and unnecessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Borzoi Dogs are funny&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Quazo&#39;s Gambit</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/quazos-gambit/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 17:38:43 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/quazos-gambit/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/quazos-gambit/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Quazo&#39;s Gambit" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quazo&amp;rsquo;s Gambit&lt;/strong&gt; is a 4 player PVP boardgame set in a fantasy magical world. Players will start with one of the four characters, each with different skills and properties. The goal of the game is store as many jewels as possible in the center bank. To achieve the goal, players can either collect jewels around the map, or steal from other players via battles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More Infos:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team Members:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matthew Kassorla&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mateo Salazar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alvin Shi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qixuan Wang&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.tabletopsimulator.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tabletop Simulator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Version of the Quazo&amp;rsquo;s Gambit: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3356045469&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3356045469&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;friendship--passion&#34;&gt;Friendship &amp;amp; Passion
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is truly a honor to work with 3 excellent artists for the creation of this fantastic boardgame. Initially I was shy and afraid to speak with people all around the world, but my teammates accept me with openness and actively shares their gaming and designing experiences. Thanks to their help, I quickly adapted to the new environment and the rich learning atmosphere of USC. To me, Quaso&amp;rsquo;s Gambit is not only a group assignment, but also a representation of our friendships and passions. It is our love for games that brought us together across barriers of geography and culture, and I am genuinely grateful to you guys! Mateo, Matt, and Alvin, thank you all ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;3.jpeg&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;play.png&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;6.jpeg&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interesting-mechanics&#34;&gt;Interesting Mechanics
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Randomness vs Certainty:&lt;/strong&gt; When discussing on how we assign the jewels to the tiles at the start of each round, we had a debate about whether to assign them randomly or regularly. After several playtests, we surprisingly found that assigning jewels randomly makes the game much more fun. The fact that random assignment somehow sacrifices fairness lead to the situation where some players are wealthy and some are poor. Thus, poor players will actively initiates battles, the only way for them to seek advantages. The wealthy ones, whose jewels got stolen, will angrily fights back, and game moves on with violence and madness(which is what we want lol)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bank Robbery:&lt;/strong&gt; Players can store jewels in their banks. If a player is near the bank, the player can rob the bank by rolling a double(roll two dice and get the same number) Initially I don&amp;rsquo;t really like the idea because it sounds too powerful. But turns out, this mechanics had really improved the gaming experience. Usually, players will rob the banks at the ending stage because it is when the banks are filled with jewels. Wealthy players usually won&amp;rsquo;t rob the banks because they need to guard theirs. For poor players, however, bank robbery is their last straw to catch. Once they succeed in robbery and escaped from battles, a brilliant comeback is made. Therefore, bank robbery had indeed adds more variability and moments of exciting suspensions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biomes:&lt;/strong&gt; Each tiles in the grid represents a type of biomes. Specific biomes give advantage to specific characters. When battling in a biome, the advantaged character can roll two dice and choose the greater one. This mechanic naturally instructs the players to move carefully around the grid, since it would be highly dangerous if they land on the biome when another character who benefits from this biome is near. This also encourage the players to stay in their own biome for safety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;12.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-i-learned&#34;&gt;What I Learned
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crazy ideas may be crazily good&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always test things out, don&amp;rsquo;t criticize right away&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Face to face meeting is important in forging strong team bonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Fish-Dang Bot: Rolling Laud</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/fish-dang-bot-rolling-laud/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 16:40:28 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/fish-dang-bot-rolling-laud/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/fish-dang-bot-rolling-laud/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Fish-Dang Bot: Rolling Laud" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fish-Dang Bot: Rolling Laud&lt;/strong&gt; is a platformer about a fish who dreams to be a dung beetle. The interesting part of this game is that players can enlarge the dung into a stepping stone via rolling them in the dung pool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More Infos:
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link to itch.io: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://zeenaz.itch.io/fish-dang-rolling-laud&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://zeenaz.itch.io/fish-dang-rolling-laud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grab-that-dung&#34;&gt;Grab that Dung!
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first coding task I was given is to write a code for the fish to grab the dung objects. Frankly speaking, I had never approached a problem like this, not even close. I was about to ask my leader to give me an easier task, but somehow I accept it, probably because I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to look down on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And this decision had made the next few hours a disaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right, it should be easy to do the grab. All I have to do is to check whether the player pressed the grab button when the dung is in player&amp;rsquo;s box trigger. As the conditions were fulfilled, I just need to attach the dung to the player. The only problem here is: how to I attach the dung to the player? After several failed trials, I was almost insane, but was still anxious to tell this to my teammates. Luckily, the leader perceived my trouble and actively offers her help. With her suggestions, I finally came up with a idea: if I simply set the dung as the children of the player, the dung will naturally moves with the player. And thus my first task is successfully done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some reflections: what makes a team a team is that members always supports each other, resulting in a &amp;ldquo;1+1 &amp;gt; 2&amp;rdquo; effect. There is no need to be timid nor worried when helped by others. Instead, it can increase the efficiency and improve our own skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;1.png&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;debugging&#34;&gt;Debugging
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the final stage of the development, a serious bug was discovered. Because everyone is busy, our leader decides to neglect the bug. However, I know that this game will become partially unplayable if the bug isn&amp;rsquo;t resolved. Therefore, I quickly finished my part and offers to debug. The bug is about jumping malfunctions on the dung platform. After an examination of the source scripts, I hypothesized that the problem is due to the ray detectors shoot out from the player. When the player stands on the dung, the rays failed to reach the dung, thereby disabling jumping(if rays detects the dung, it will change player status to grounded, so jumping would be allowed) The bug was them solved by simply adding new ray that shoots further. Personally, I think this is my greatest contribution to the team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;3.png&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;dream&#34;&gt;Dream
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a fish can become a dung beetle, then there should be no way I can&amp;rsquo;t be a game designer XD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;2.png&#34; width=50%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;important-lessons&#34;&gt;Important Lessons
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing progress is required, use professional platforms such as GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always make sure the members are using the same Unity versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;do not touch the project files of others!!!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>By Your Side</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/by-your-side/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 14:39:10 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/by-your-side/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/by-your-side/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post By Your Side" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By Your Side&lt;/strong&gt; is a rhythm game centered around the theme of school bullying. The game tells narrates via the diary of a boy abused by his classmates. One notable feature is the notes players will encounter. Aside from traditional notes in rhythm games, I add some new notes to enrich the game content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;1.png&#34; width=33%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;2.png&#34; width=33%&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;3.png&#34; width=33%&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-infos&#34;&gt;More Infos
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link to itch.io: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://kiriloler.itch.io/by-your-side&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://kiriloler.itch.io/by-your-side&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-thoughts&#34;&gt;Personal Thoughts
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;beginning&#34;&gt;Beginning
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is my first attempt on developing a game from scratch. From scripts and art assets to stories and animations, I faced so many challenges that almost made me give up. There are times when I completely lost focus, times when I can&amp;rsquo;t understands the codes I wrote, times when I want to delete the art works I made. Tough and frustrating, I gradually learn from those experiences. I start to add annotations to my codes, properly organize my files, and cope with my anxiousness when the outcomes are disappointing. Over months of developments and iterations, I finally came up with a completed playable prototype. Looking back from now, &lt;em&gt;By Your Side&lt;/em&gt; might not be my best project, but it is my favorite one. Those painful memories I do not wish to recap is also the ones that embraced me during difficult times, encouraged me to move on. &lt;em&gt;I had been through harsh times, and I will get through this one too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;BG copy.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;Music
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be honest, the soundtracks I made for this game is kinda unpolished. For each music piece, I simply add a main instrument for melody and a drum for beats. Still, I do love those soundtracks, probably maybe because me as creator tend to neglect the drawbacks of my works. But, partly, I love them because they echoes the melodies in my heart. The delightfulness, hopes and dreams in the playground, the distress, oppression when abused, the hollow, illusional voices in dreams&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;I had put them into this small, simple soundtrack, and I hope you enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;lisa&#34;&gt;Lisa
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roses are no longer the red of pain,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skies shall not anymore be blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May the world immersed in purple rain,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I fallen to you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About Me</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;im-an-amateur-game-developer-from-china-and-i-especially-love-to-play-metroidvania-platformer-and-rhythm-games&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an amateur game developer from China, and I especially LOVE to play Metroidvania, platformer, and rhythm games!
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#34;here-are-some-basic-information-about-myself&#34;&gt;Here are some basic information about myself:
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email✉: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mailto:kiriloler126@outlook.com&#34; &gt;kiriloler126@outlook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birthdate🎂: 2007/01/26&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hobbies💻: Gaming, Rock Climbing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;itch.io page: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://kiriloler.itch.io/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;itch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bilibili page: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://space.bilibili.com/456724990&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;bilibili&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;youtube page: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@kevinwang4288&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;youtube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;thank-you-for-visiting-my-blog&#34;&gt;Thank you for visiting my blog!
&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are some useful links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
